<resources>
    <string name="app_name">sdk</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="x_close">X</string>

    <string name="paragrap1">Advertising is a marketing communication that employs an openly sponsored, non-personal message to promote or sell a product, service or idea</string>
    <string name="paragrap2">Sponsors of advertising are typically businesses wishing to promote their products or services. Advertising is differentiated from public relations in that an advertiser pays for and has control over the message. It differs from personal selling in that the message is non-personal, i.e., not directed to a particular individual.</string>
    <string name="paragrap3">Advertising is communicated through various mass media,[2] including traditional media such as newspapers, magazines, television, radio, outdoor advertising or direct mail; and new media such as search results, blogs, social media, websites or text messages. The actual presentation of the message in a medium is referred to as an advertisement (advert or ad for short).</string>
    <string name="paragrap4">Commercial advertisements often seek to generate increased consumption of their products or services through "branding", which associates a product name or image with certain qualities in the minds of consumers. On the other hand, ads that intend to elicit an immediate sale are known as direct-response advertising. Non-commercial entities that advertise more than consumer products or services include political parties, interest groups, religious organizations and governmental agencies. Non-profit organizations may use free modes of persuasion, such as a public service announcement. Advertising may also help to reassure employees or shareholders that a company is viable or successful.</string>


    <string name="geofences_added">Geofences added</string>
    <string name="geofences_removed">Geofences removed</string>

    <string name="geofence_not_available">Geofence service is not available now</string>
    <string name="geofence_too_many_geofences">Your app has registered too many geofences</string>
    <string name="geofence_too_many_pending_intents">
        You have provided too many PendingIntents to the addGeofences() call
    </string>
    <string name="unknown_geofence_error">
        Unknown error: the Geofence service is not available now
    </string>
    <string name="geofence_transition_invalid_type">
        Geofence transition error: invalid transition type %1$d
    </string>

    <!-- Transition type strings -->
    <string name="geofence_transition_entered">Entered</string>
    <string name="geofence_transition_exited">Exited</string>
    <string name="unknown_geofence_transition">Unknown Transition</string>
    <!--<string name="ad_tag_url2"><![CDATA[https://rvphp.djaxbidder.com/demo_advancedvast/fc.php?script=rmVideo&zoneid=12&format=vast3]]></string> -->
    <!--&ndash;&gt; <string name="ad_SDK_tag_url2"><![CDATA[https://revphpe.djaxbidder.com/AdmobileadSDK541/www/admin/plugins/mobileAdsDelivery/vast3xml.php?zoneid=42&campaignid=6&bannerid=43]]></string>-->
<!--    <string name="ad_SDK_tag_url2"><![CDATA[https://rvphp.djaxbidder.com//enterprise_videodev//YWRz//d3d3//vast3xml.php?zoneid=205&campaignid=189&bannerid=504&adtype=%27inters%27]]></string>-->
    <string name="ad_SDK_tag_url2"><![CDATA[https://revphpe.djaxbidder.com/advancedsdk/www/admin/plugins/mobileAdsDelivery/vast3xml.php?zoneid=94&campaignid=8&bannerid=53&adtype=%27in-article%27]]></string>

</resources>
